CURRICULUM VITAE			
NAME	ACTUAL POSITION		
Antonio Trabalza	Frelance Full Stack Developer		
https://antoniotrkdz.github.io   antoniotrabalza@gmail.com   TEL +44(0)7577833827   +393204516210			
EDUCATION/QUALIFICATIONS			
INSTITUTION AND LOCATION	DEGREE	YEAR(S)	FIELD OF STUDY
Founders & Coders London	London Curriculum	2017	Full stack web development
Imperial College London	Course	2015	C for Science
NIMR London - MRC	Course	2014	Successful Grant Writing
Imperial College London	License	2010	ASpA Personal License
"Sapienza" University of Rome	PhD	2006-2009	Neuroscience
"Sapienza" University of Rome	B.A.	1999-2005	General and Experimental Psychology

#### About

I am a web developer with Neuroscience research experience. I am passionate about science and technology and I love the free software world: Devuan and Void GNU/Linux – (Neo)Vim – Blockchain.

I write mainly JavaScript, VUE.js, Node.js and Java EE, I also have experience with Ruby (on Rails). I have been studying and using GNU/Linux for more than 20 years and I have installed, configured and used many distributions on the most diverse hardware: from HPC servers to laptops to Chromebooks. I use Containers and Virtual Machines, and among circuits and components I have fun to make Arduino and Raspberry Pi projects.

#### Skills

## Programming – Github profile name: antoniotrkdz

- Javascript ES6, HTML5 e CSS3.
- VUE.js, React, Redux and JQuery.
- Java EE and Ruby on Rails.
- Wordpress.
- Shell scripting.
- BEM, Bootstrap 3.\* and 4, Material design.
- Node.js Express.js, Hapi.js and Handelbars.
- PostgreSQL and MySQL.
- Testing and CI: Rspec, OUnit, Tape, Travis CI, Jest, Codecov.
- C relatively to Arduino prototyping.
- Python relatively to Raspberry Pi prototyping.
- · R Statistics.
- OpenSCAD (3D design and printing).
- Macro language for FIJI/ImageJ2 Tools for image analisys (microscopy) & pattern recognition (see https://antoniotrkdz.github.io).

### IT / System Administration

- Gnu/Linux Operating System.
- Shell (bash) scripting.
- Installation and Administration of Ubuntu, Debian, Gentoo, Fedora, CentOS and Devuan, both Desktop and Server.

- Configuration and (remote) administration of LAMP and similar stacks, tests and log analysis (SAR tools).
- Network analysis (nmap, netstat, netcat, tcpdump, wireshark).
- · Heroku deployment, basic AWS skills.
- Virtualization VirtualBox and Qemu/KVM.
- Docker Containers.
- Very good hardware knowledge.
- Good Electronics knowledge.

# Interpersonal, Planning and Problem solving

- Presentation of Code, Tech and related subjects and Product pitch, both written and oral.
- Presentation of Research findings in international journals publications, at conferences and regular Laboratory and Department meetings, both written and oral.
- Managing, planning and reporting of my own work and supervised students (20+).
- Management of internal and external collaborations.
- Design and planning of novel experiments to overcome problems related to PhD and PostDoc research activities.
- Management of Research funds.
- Fluent English both written and spoken.

## **Working Experience:**

# July 2019 to February 2020:

Full Stack developer – Engine S.r.l. – Serre di Rapolano (SI).

Developed a cloud system to manage traffic cameras remotely: Celeritas Cloud.

To be deployed during 2020.

## September 2018 to February 2019:

Network systems admin and Developer – Dimensione Solare S.r.l. – Notaresco (TE). Write MiSE application to "Fabbrica intelligente" Funding: ASTRA – Advanced training system using Blockchain to certificate accomplishments and qualifications.

Under evaluation: achieved pre-funding stage.

### May to August 2018:

Web Developer - Nebulab.it - Pescara.

## **February 2018 to May 2018:**

Web Development and Javascript teacher – Turn into Coders – Torino.

### February 2017 to December 2017:

Web Developer – Founders & Coders C.I.C. – London.

Stem Ambassador Web Development teacher – London.

# **May 2016 to February 2017:**

Employed as Postdoc Research Associate at Department of Cellular and Molecular Neuroscience, Imperial College Faculty of Medicine – London, funded by BTRC – Brain Tumour Research Committee.

### **June 2014 to November 2015:**

Employed as Postdoc Research Associate at MRC – Clinical Sciences Centre, Imperial College Hammersmith Hospital Campus – London, funded by MRC core funding.

### May 2010 to March 2014:

Employed as Postdoc Research Associate at Department of Cellular and Molecular Neuroscience, Imperial College Faculty of Medicine – London, funded by ERC grant - "Improved retrograde lentiviral vectors for gene therapy in motor neuron disease".

### **Teaching Experience**

Two courses (2007/2008 and 2008/2009) relative to the main lectures of Applied Biology course of the Faculty of Psychology – University "Sapienza" of Rome – 3 lectures (6 hours total) each year. One course (10 hours total) of Web Development for children age 10-16 years. STEM ambassador activity – London (2017).